{"data":[{"question":"She made me to pay for the damage I had done.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"made","b":"to pay","c":"for","d":"had done","answer":"2","explain":"- To pay-> pay","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"He warned me to make an eye on my luggage as that place was full of thieves.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"me","b":"to make","c":"on","d":"full","answer":"2","explain":"- To make-> to keep\nkeep an eye on: pay attention to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"When you are late for class, you should apologize for your teacher.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"for","c":"should","d":"for","answer":"4","explain":"- For-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The village that I was born and grew up is situated on the Red River.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"that","b":"grew","c":"situated","d":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- That-> where","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Some children, before going to school, go to kindergartens, officially are called nursery schools.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"before","b":"go","c":"officially","d":"are called","answer":"4","explain":"- Are called-> called","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"English children start school in six and finish at sixteen.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"English","b":"start","c":"in","d":"at","answer":"3","explain":"- In-> at","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't feel as tired after a train journey so I do after a car journey.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"don't","b":"tired","c":"so","d":"after","answer":"3","explain":"- So-> as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The child ran fastly to get to school.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"child","b":"fastly","c":"to","d":"school","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Fastly-> fast","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"If it will rain this afternoon, we will have to cancel our picnic.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"If","b":"will rain","c":"will","d":"cancel","answer":"2","explain":"- Will rain-> rains","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"He is very weak to lift this suitcase.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"very","b":"weak","c":"to","d":"this","answer":"1","explain":"- Very-> too","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}